
/* HtmlCSS Quiz Questions 
 * creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers 
 */

let questions = [

/* Q1 */     
	{
      numb: 1,
      question: "CSS stands for -",
      options: [
                "A) Cascade style sheets",
                "B) Color and style sheets",
                "C) Cascading style sheets",
                "D) None of the above"
               ],
      answer: "C) Cascading style sheets"
    },
/*Copy till here*/


/* Q2 */     
	{
      numb: 2,
      question: "The property in CSS used to change the background color of an element is -",
      options: [
                "A) bgcolor",
                "B) color",
                "C) background-color",
                "D) All of the above"
               ],
      answer: "C) background-color"
    },
/*Copy till here*/

/* Q3 */     
	{
      numb: 3,
      question: "The CSS property used to control the element's font-size is -",
      options: [
                "A) text-style",
                "B) text-size",
                "C) font-size",
                "D) None of the above"
               ],
      answer: "C) font-size"
    },
/*Copy till here*/
	
/* Q4 */     
	{
      numb: 4,
      question: "Which of the following CSS property is used to set the background image of an element?",
      options: [
                "A) background-attachment",
                "B) background-image",
                "C) background-color",
                "D) None of the above"
               ],
      answer: "B) background-image"
    },
/*Copy till here*/
	
/* Q5 */     
	{
      numb: 5,
      question: "Are the negative values allowed in padding property?",
      options: [
                "A) Yes",
                "B) No",
                "C) Can't say",
                "D) May be"
               ],
      answer: "B) No"
    },
/*Copy till here*/

/* Q6 */     
	{
      numb: 6,
      question: "Which of the following property is used as the shorthand property of margin properties?",
      options: [
                "A) margin-left",
                "B) margin-right",
                "C) margin",
                "D) None of the above"
               ],
      answer: "C) margin"
    },
/*Copy till here*/

/* Q7 */     
	{
      numb: 7,
      question: "The CSS property used to specify the transparency of an element is -",
      options: [
                "A) opacity",
                "B) filter",
                "C) visibility",
                "D) overlay"
               ],
      answer: "A) opacity"
    },
/*Copy till here*/

/* Q8 */ 
	{
      numb: 8,
      question: "How to select the elements with the class name 'example'?",
      options: [
                "A) .example",
                "B) .#example",
                "C) example",
                "D) .Class example"
               ],
      answer: "A) .example"
    },
/*Copy till here*/

/* Q9 */ 
	{
      numb: 9,
      question: "Which of the following is the correct syntax to select the p siblings of a div element?",
      options: [
                "A) p",
                "B) div + p",
                "C) div p",
                "D) div ~ p"
               ],
      answer: "D) div ~ p"
    },
/*Copy till here*/


/* Q10 */    
	{
      numb: 10,
      question: "The CSS property used to set the distance between the borders of the adjacent cells in the table is -",
      options: [
                "A) border-collapse",
                "B) border-radius",
                "C) border-spacing",
                "D) None of the above"
               ],
      answer: "C) border-spacing"
    },
/*Copy till here*/


]; /* Array close*/